mightycall.com 2013-10-18

# MightyCall Privacy Policy

Welcome to the MightyCall.com Web site of Infratel US, Inc., a Washington corporation (together with its affiliates, “Infratel,” “we,” or “us”). This privacy policy covers the website and services made available from infratel.com, mightycall.com or otherwise by Infratel (referred to in this policy collectively as the “Service”).

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice describing our collection, use and disclosure of information, including personal information, that may be collected in connection with our Service. This policy is incorporated and subject to our Terms of Use located at [link to Terms of Use] and, if you subscribe to paid portions of our Service, this policy is also incorporated and subject to our Terms of Service <http://www.mightycall.com/terms.html> or other service agreement.

**Personal Information**

When we discuss “personal information” in this policy, we are referring to information that may be used to identify an individual, such as a person’s name, address, email address, telephone number, or credit card. We collect personal information in the course of providing our Service to you and you may also make personal information available to others as you use our Service. Below are some examples of the types of personal information we collect through the Service and the ways in which we use it.

**How We Collect Personal Information**

We collect personal information in the course of providing our Service to you, including through your voluntary, optional submissions, such as information that you provide to us at the time of registering for our Service, or through your use of our Service. When you register with us for an account, we may collect information such as your name, company name, business title, address, email address, and phone numbers. When you pay for certain features of the Service, we may collect information such as your credit or debit card number, expiration date, and CVV or security code number. You may also provide personal information to us in other ways, such as by requesting customer support or product information.

We may also receive personal information from third parties about their users, and may combine this information with other personal information we maintain about you. If we do so, this policy also governs the combined information.

**How We Use Personal Information**

We use personal information we collect to provide, improve, and develop our Service, to tailor your user experience, to respond to your inquiries or requests, to prevent or investigate fraudulent or inappropriate usage of our Service, for research and development, to analyze trends, and for the other purposes described in this policy.

If you are a subscriber to a paid portion of the Service, you will receive occasional alerts and email messages to inform you of system status, billing issues, payment processing and other day to day activities necessary to keep you informed about your subscription. In addition, we may use your personal information to deliver targeted marketing messages. You may opt-out from receiving marketing messages by following the instructions provided in the messages or by emailing the address provided at the end of this policy, but you will continue to receive bills, customer service-related alerts and emails.

**How We Share Personal Information**

In the course of providing the Service, we may share your personal information with third party service providers such as payment service providers and Service hosters. We may also provide personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of providing our Service and for our other purposes described in this policy. We limit the personal information shared with these third parties to that which is necessary to carry out those functions.

We may also share personal information with third parties (including regulatory or law enforcement authorities) in order to carry out a user’s request or if we believe that doing so is legally required or is in our interest to protect our property or other legal rights (including, but not limited to, enforcement of our agreements), or the rights or property of others.

**Non-Personal Information We Collect, and How We Use I** t

We may also collect information that is not personally identifiable, and may aggregate personal information or otherwise render it anonymous (that is, non-personally identifiable). We may use non-personally identifiable information we collect to provide, improve, and develop our Service and otherwise to tailor your user experience, to prevent or investigate fraudulent or inappropriate usage of our Service, for research and development, and for the other purposes described in this policy. We may use this anonymous information for various purposes and may share it with third parties. Below are some examples of the types of non-personal information we collect and some specific examples of how we use this information:

Usage tracking. We may collect non-personal information from your use of our Service. For example, we may collect information about user traffic and usage patterns throughout our site, and similar information regarding the use of our Service, as well as review stored voicemails and recorded phone calls. We may also track click-through information, such as IP addresses, from the messages we send to our users. We use the information we collect in these manners to, for example, improve our Service, to develop new products and services, to discourage and address abusive and fraudulent use of our Service, and to help our users with troubleshooting issues.  

Methods of collection. We collect non-personal information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “Web beacons”). When you visit our site or use our Service, we may send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer, mobile device, tablet, or similar device that uniquely identifies your browser or recognizes a cookie that is already on your device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, and to customize your experience. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Also, please be aware that third parties may set cookies on your hard drive or use other means of passively collecting information about your use of their services or content. We do not have access to, or control over, these third-party means of passive data collection.  
If we directly combine any non-personal information gathered through passive means with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information under this policy. Otherwise, we use information collected by passive means in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable forms.

**International Visitors**

Users from outside the United States should be aware that they are submitting their information to servers within the United States and that they may not be entitled to protections and remedies provided under laws of their places of residence. By providing personal information to us, you consent to the transfer of it to the United States and the use of it in accordance with this policy.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we or our third party service providers have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Please be aware, however, that no data transmissions over the Internet or other networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security or integrity of any information you transmit to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk. Once we receive personal information, we make reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. But we cannot represent or guarantee that personal information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. We do require that all subscribers to paid portions of our Service maintain a personal user id and password. At no time may user ids and passwords be shared among multiple people.

If we learn of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may post a notice through the Service if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to access the Service. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

**Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. Children under 13 are not authorized to create accounts on Infratel.com or otherwise use the Service.

**Third-Party Sites and Services**

Our Service may contain links to and interoperate with third-party sites and services. Any links to or interoperability with third-party sites or services are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties. Any personal information that you provide to any other third party is subject to that third party’s privacy practices and policies, not this policy. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

**Business transfers**

Information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of company assets, as well as in the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of our business assets.

**Information Retention and Disposal**

We may retain personal information for as long as we have a business need for it or as applicable laws or regulations or government orders require us to retain it.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

If your personal information changes in any way, we invite you to correct or update your information as soon as possible. You can make updates to your profile information by logging into your account on infratel.com at any time. You can also request changes or access to your information by emailing cloudsupport@infratel.com. We will only discuss account specifics with the owner of the account.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may change this policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this policy, we will change the “last updated” date above. If there are material changes to this policy, we will notify you more directly. We encourage you to check this policy whenever you use our Web sites and services to understand how your personal information is used.

**Contacting Us**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please send written correspondence to:

C/O Privacy Concerns for infratel.com  
Infratel Inc.  
1424 4th Ave  
Suite 900  
Seattle, WA 98101  
cloudsupport at infratel dot com
